MOHAMMAD RINALDI

Gg. Mesjid 4, Cibubur, Ciracas, Jakarta Timur · 081297159759 moh.rnldi@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/ mohammad rinaldi · https:// mohrinaldi.netlify.a pp/

I am a final year student of informatics systems with a strong focus on Product Design, passionate about research, problem solving, human-centered design, and interface design. My previous work experience was UI/UX Designer, Product Designer with a track record of collaborating in Operating System Development. I also developed myself through multimedia organizations on campus as well as online learning classes and the experience of participating in PKM competitions on campus.

EXPERIENCE

JANUARY 2022 – JUNE 2022

INTERN UI/UX DESIGNER, PT. TELKOM INDONESIA

- Collaborate with PMs and Developers to make all requirements aligned with business needs and objectives
- Collaborate with the research team to be able to solve problems
- Analyzed and defined problem based on user behavior using design thinking method
- Designing mobile-based application user interfaces, websites and dashboards for projects in progress within 6 months using Figma
- Provide illustration assets needed for user interface display needs

AUGUST 2021 – DECEMBER 2021

INTERN UX DESIGNER. TEMAN PASAR

- Analyzed and defined problem based on user behavior using design thinking method
- Designed the user interface mobile-based application, company profile website, and dashboard within 3 months using Figma and Adobe Illustration
- Collaborated with web and mobile developers to produce application based on user needs and business goals using content management and collaboration software including Slack and Trello
- Completed 3 mobile-based user interface design for TemanPasar Mobile App, TemanAntar Mobile App, TemanPedagang Mobile App, TemanPasar Company Profile Website, and Administrative Dashboard. Design has been implemented and used.

MEI 2021 – AUGUST 2021

INTERN UX DESIGNER, PT. ALAN MEDIATECH INDONESIA

- Collaborated with PMs and Developers to making all the requirements align with the client need and business goal
- Completed redesign the company profile website and product app

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION SYSTEMS 3.34/4.00, UNIVERSITAS

MUHAMMADIYAH PROF. DR HAMKA

- Completed Web Programming and Human-Computer Interaction subjects and got an A score.
- Selected as a student who follows a program from BUMN, namely the Certified Student Internship Program (PMMB)

2015 - 2018

VISUAL COMMUNICATION DESIGN GRADUATE 3.31/4.00, SMKN 58 JAKARTA

• Get a competency certificate from the Erlangga institution

SKILLS

- Design Thinking
- Interface Design
- Wireframing
- Prototyping
- Usability Testing
- Web Design
- UI Animation

- Problem Solving
- Collaboration
- Leadership
- Good Time Management
- Creative

PROJECT

2022

SAIKA (CHAT APPLICATION AND SELF DEVELOPMENT), UNIVERSITAS

MUHAMMADIYAH PROF. DR HAMKA

- Conduct research to solve problems encountered before working on the project
- Create an interface and also a prototype of the application

2022

MONITORING SAPI, PT. TELKOM INDONESIA

- Conduct research to solve problems encountered before working on the project
- Create an interface and also a prototype of the application
- Provide illustration assets needed for user interface display needs
- Collaborate with Developers to align all requirements needed

2021

MUYAA.ID, PT. ALAN MEDIATECH INDONESIA

- Create an interface and also a prototype of the application
- Collaborate with PMs and Developers to make all requirements aligned with business needs and objectives
- Provide illustration assets needed for user interface display needs